I wear the black shirt
Tengo la camisa negra
Today my love is in mourning
Hoy mi amor está de luto
Today I have a sorrow in my soul
Hoy tengo en el alma una pena
And it's because of your spell
Y es por culpa de tu embrujo
Today I know that you no longer love me
Hoy sé que tu ya no me quieres
And that's what hurts me the most
Y eso es lo que más me hiere
That I wear the black shirt
Que tengo la camisa negra
And a sorrow that hurts me
Y una pena que me duele
Sadly it seems that I was left alone
Mal parece que solo me quedé
And your lie was completely pure
Y fue pura todita tu mentira
What damn bad luck of mine
Que maldita mala suerte la mía
that that day I found you
Que aquel día te encontré
For drinking the evil poison of your love
Por beber del veneno malevo de tu amor
I was left dying and full of pain
Yo quedé moribundo y lleno de dolor
I breathed in that bitter smoke of your goodbye
Respiré de ese humo amargo de tu adiós
And since you left I only...
Y desde que tú te fuiste yo solo...
wear, I wear the black shirt
tengo, tengo la camisa negra
Because I have a black soul
Porque negra tengo el alma
I lost my calm because of you and almost lost my bed
Yo por ti perdí la calma y casi pierdo hasta mi cama
Bed, bed, come on baby
Cama, cama, come on baby
I tell you covertly
Te digo con disimulo
I wear the black shirt and underneath I am deceased
Tengo la camisa negra y debajo tengo el difunto
Your love doesn't interest me anymore
Ya tu amor no me interesa
What tasted like glory to me yesterday, today tastes like pure (sh)...
Lo que ayer me supo a gloria, hoy me sabe a pura...
Wednesday afternoon and you don't arrive
Miércoles por la tarde y tu que no llegas
Not even showing signs
Ni siquiera muestras señas
And me with the black shirt and your suitcases at the door
Y yo con la camisa negra y tus maletas en la puerta
Sadly it seems that I was left alone
Mal parece que solo me quedé
And your lie was completely pure
Y fue pura todita tu mentira
What damn bad luck of mine
Que maldita mala suerte la mía
that that day I found you
Que aquel día te encontré
For drinking the evil poison of your love
Por beber del veneno malevo de tu amor
I was left dying and full of pain
Yo quedé moribundo y lleno de dolor
I breathed in that bitter smoke of your goodbye
Respiré de ese humo amargo de tu adiós
And since you left, I only
Y desde que tú te fuiste yo solo...
wear, I wear the black shirt
tengo, tengo la camisa negra
Because I have a black soul
Porque negra tengo el alma
I lost my calm because of you and almost lost my bed
Yo por ti perdí la calma y casi pierdo hasta mi cama
Bed, bed, come on baby
Cama, cama, come on baby
I tell you covertly
Te digo con disimulo
I wear the black shirt and underneath I am deceased
Tengo la camisa negra y debajo tengo el difunto
Because I have a black soul
Porque negra tengo el alma
I lost my calm because of you and almost lost my bed
Yo por ti perdí la calma y casi pierdo hasta mi cama
Bed, bed, come on baby
Cama, cama, come on baby
I tell you covertly
Te digo con disimulo
I wear the black shirt and underneath I am deceased
Tengo la camisa negra y debajo tengo el difunto